<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Scroll Plugins</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="demo_scrollview">ScrollView</string>
    <string name="demo_abslist">AbsListView</string>

    <string name="ipsum">Chillwave banh mi ennui, craft beer gentrify Tumblr cliche quinoa whatever Marfa gastropub High Life actually Vice Pitchfork. Slow-carb YOLO raw denim McSweeney\'s. Vice distillery Carles tousled fap, wolf kale chips American Apparel small batch. Godard lo-fi hella, wolf mixtape leggings locavore Carles pug. Banksy gentrify locavore distillery iPhone sustainable. Jean shorts seitan tote bag shabby chic McSweeney\'s, deep v fingerstache viral vinyl Schlitz iPhone leggings bespoke try-hard chia. Selfies Williamsburg pop-up single-origin coffee mixtape, yr fanny pack.

Keytar keffiyeh tousled, XOXO VHS jean shorts PBR Marfa Neutra retro flannel try-hard gluten-free. Seitan photo booth XOXO irony. Quinoa church-key bespoke sartorial bitters banjo. Trust fund salvia art party mustache banh mi. Selfies fap semiotics pickled slow-carb. Kitsch 3 wolf moon Marfa, Wes Anderson fashion axe put a bird on it Etsy freegan DIY hella Neutra Pitchfork. Brooklyn Neutra tofu yr, wayfarers fixie deep v Schlitz viral trust fund craft beer keytar dreamcatcher tote bag PBR.

Austin tote bag Kickstarter, bespoke you probably haven\'t heard of them next level butcher cray Shoreditch small batch occupy tousled +1 before they sold out fixie. Typewriter Cosby sweater swag crucifix yr, sustainable bicycle rights. Paleo biodiesel Helvetica blog, kogi Vice tote bag irony direct trade Tonx Godard. Portland fashion axe butcher bitters Echo Park, four loko wolf synth direct trade Tonx cardigan Austin. 90\'s keytar retro normcore ennui yr polaroid ugh, DIY bicycle rights. PBRB hella Portland bitters, you probably haven\'t heard of them crucifix mixtape polaroid 90\'s PBR. Lomo American Apparel meh paleo Tonx.

Vice cornhole stumptown 90\'s, Odd Future quinoa pour-over. Typewriter fap lomo, High Life Carles distillery Bushwick food truck Williamsburg polaroid keytar Tonx irony Pitchfork farm-to-table. Godard Odd Future leggings gentrify selfies Bushwick. Master cleanse banjo food truck, roof party biodiesel dreamcatcher farm-to-table freegan pop-up McSweeney\'s. Leggings occupy fanny pack Vice small batch. Forage American Apparel mixtape Helvetica next level, Wes Anderson Carles Portland PBRB post-ironic asymmetrical Cosby sweater keffiyeh. Tote bag Portland VHS, twee pour-over flannel literally Cosby sweater retro Brooklyn sustainable.

Umami DIY fixie, gastropub fap ethical actually slow-carb put a bird on it Kickstarter Odd Future ethnic. Gastropub butcher +1, actually retro single-origin coffee food truck typewriter pour-over Intelligentsia. Crucifix sustainable XOXO farm-to-table, High Life fixie ugh wolf Thundercats you probably haven\'t heard of them plaid organic. Drinking vinegar plaid kale chips leggings gentrify cardigan. 90\'s Pitchfork before they sold out typewriter craft beer artisan chambray small batch, readymade deep v. Blue Bottle Godard fap, wolf salvia keffiyeh stumptown plaid Cosby sweater deep v occupy Schlitz shabby chic chambray. +1 Carles beard authentic direct trade normcore.
Oh. You need a little dummy text for your mockup? How quaint.

I bet you’re still using Bootstrap too…</string>
</resources>
